<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python on izdwuut's personal place</title><link>/tags/python/</link><description>Recent content in Python on izdwuut's personal place</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 13:37:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create Reddit upvoter using Python and PRAW</title><link>/tutorials/reddit-upvoter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 13:37:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/reddit-upvoter/</guid><description>Welcome to another tutorial of mine! Be sure to check the previous ones here. In this one, I&amp;rsquo;m going to cover a script that upvotes every new submission and comment from a given subreddit. Please, don&amp;rsquo;t try to run it in reverse and downvote all the things. Please&amp;hellip;
I assume that you have Python installed on your system. The tutorial targets Windows 10 with Powershell.
Registering the application In order to use PRAW, we need to register our script first.</description></item><item><title>Host a Flask app using Apache and mod_wsgi</title><link>/tutorials/apache-wsgi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 13:37:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/apache-wsgi/</guid><description>Now that dust has settled after Youtube Thumbnail Downloader tutorial, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new thing. When you run a Flask developement server, it tells you that it isn&amp;rsquo;t suited for prodution:
WARNING: This is a developlment server. Do not use it in a production deployment.
Fair point. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been tested for security and whatnot. There are a few alternatives, most notably Nginx and Apache. I go for the latter.</description></item><item><title>Create your own Youtube Thumbnail Downloader in Python</title><link>/tutorials/youtube-thumbnail-downloader/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 11:36:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/youtube-thumbnail-downloader/</guid><description>The idea is pretty simple. Given the URL to a Youtube video, the script spews out it&amp;rsquo;s thumbnail. See this lovely image? It would make for a perfect wallpaper and I wrote a script that does just that.
How would Python render it possible, you&amp;rsquo;d ask? By working hand-in-hand with Youtube API, of course! I should seriously reconsider becoming a clown. I have a hunch that it would come as natural to me.</description></item></channel></rss>